Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 544 records, 1930-2013 IBT0051
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Teamster Records, Series 4
  - Ledgers and Record Books, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1937; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 149, Ledger data_value_missing_25486d8e849e1fba83da823ed04b68e6)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1938; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 149, Ledger data_value_missing_d296b327bfe2b5ff303f20bf46bc0464)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1938; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 149, Ledger data_value_missing_2f2c021b5ab5be9b8580f627748a5247)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1936-1937; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 150, Ledger data_value_missing_f0627cd1ed7475ed550e2bf699c421d4)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1938-1939; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 151, Ledger data_value_missing_21a1b2b1004ee465f3b019a7ccaf333a)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1940-1941; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 152, Ledger data_value_missing_5e24ff673fbcf1d000f3b654c4f6624f)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1942-1943; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 152, Ledger data_value_missing_d358757b061536b1ec49e1a92d4aca0a)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1944-1945; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 153, Ledger data_value_missing_c6b5241b92835ec253e0dde399f0cef9)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1946-1947; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 153, Ledger data_value_missing_2f4fb8c9520ff256c4e374d550fbd8e4)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1942-1943; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 154)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1944-1945; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 155)
    - Local 387 Ledger, 1946-1947; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 156)
    - Local 387 Minute Book, 1950-1953; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 146, Ledger data_value_missing_1b5e22d8e0a25b2625a2c7ba4a002d66)
    - Local 387 Minute Book, 1954-1959; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 146, Ledger data_value_missing_f23d0a560fecea764970ebbcb529ecd9)
    - Local 387 Minute Book, 1959-1965; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 146, Ledger data_value_missing_77a49ee9cf741fe5fa6f328404009265)
    - Local 387 Minute Book, 1965-1974; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Ledger data_value_missing_0e6bf47a44c05dcc8c02fc2e2d812e54)
    - Local 387 Minute Book, 1974-1985; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 147, Ledger data_value_missing_772e41b939b0abb2c7730d65bc5b5cec)
    - Record Book, 1972-1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 144, Folder 9)
- Ephemera, Series 5
  The patches, stickers, and photographs are grouped by similar items and put in folders, which are alphabetically arranged. The other objects are grouped and stored according to like objects.
  The materials of this series include cassettes and VHS tapes, patches, stickers, photographs, t-shirts, hats, banners and posters, and a notary press. The materials of this series are from Locals 387, 487, and 544. These materials range in date from 1937-2001, though many of the items are undated.
  - Banner, "Teamsters Local 387 Des Moines, Iowa" [1/2], undated; Series 5 (Drawer 8, Banner data_value_missing_f95779a41fb5c4f01f585e1b4760cf00)
  - Banner, "Teamsters Local 387 Des Moines, Iowa" [2/2], undated; Series 5 (Drawer 8, Banner data_value_missing_15cb4727257027b8c9fe21d07beeb15a)
  - Bumper stickers and decals, undated; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Cassette, "Out of Order: 'How Ron Carey Highjacked the Teamsters Convention'", undated; Series 5 (Box 158, Cassette data_value_missing_c5c4cb03391d36c57f2e1a1537d66257)
  - Cassette, "Proud to be a Teamster" [1/2], 1986; Series 5 (Box 158, Cassette data_value_missing_f9908eac5f96a9dd4488ef1519bb6340)
  - Cassette, "Proud to be a Teamster" [2/2], 1986; Series 5 (Box 158, Cassette data_value_missing_e2be2b6ade631191fceedfd8cfdef6fa)
  - Hat, "DRIVE", undated; Series 5 (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_409f18684aeba6f5c26dee00013c6ff9)
  - Hat, "Minnesota U.L.C.", 1994; Series 5 (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_d0d843987e200a184d0369e860605275)
  - Hat, "Super Valu", undated; Series 5 (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_db97bf450fcba3e59a2f8ade30e97c8d)
  - Hat, "Teamsters", undated; Series (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_e48d736b9fd92d7b8ff66ccefbf37989)
  - Hat, "United Foods, Inc.", undated; Series 5 (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_de3ddba1d50d9c48bce2e1b91a2906b1)
  - Local 487 Certificate of Affiliation, 1937; Series 5 (Drawer 8, Poster data_value_missing_50e9b140e253fa602b7135cf3937ba5f)
  - Notary Press, Local 487, undated; Series 5 (Box 159, Object data_value_missing_7505d6c1433e5c3c9242b5c5dd1bcb67)
  - Patches - American Trucking Association, undated; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Patches, undated; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Local 487, 1973-1976; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Local 544 Stemm Transfer Strike, 1986; Series 5 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Poster, "To the Public" Consumer Boycott [1/2], undated; Series 5 (Drawer 8, Poster data_value_missing_9f9f49ec200c421599241c3f9503d3d9)
  - Poster, "To the Public" Consumer Boycott [2/2], undated; Series 5 (Drawer 8, Poster data_value_missing_4bd041a9d47a5d369b4dee13524e0555)
  - T-shirt, "Las Vegas 2001 Teamsters" [1/2], Series 5 (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_188404b902f75502497db1a8f51d7ba9)
  - T-shirt, "Las Vegas 2001 Teamsters" [2/2], Series 5 (Box 157, Object data_value_missing_cb11be50d79aa70ce6ad518759b21bf3)
  - VHS tape, "Hoffa for Teamster President!" CBS's "Eye-to-Eye Show 7/27/95 and Larry King Live 8/30/95 Featuring Jimmy Hoffa, 1995; Series 5 (Box 158, Videocassette data_value_missing_1237c6face18c15d757cda3afa61ac00)
  - VHS tape, "Out of Order: 'How Ron Carey Highjacked the Teamsters Convention", undated; Series 5 (Box 158, Videocassette data_value_missing_167342c6cbaef52e9ca856eaa0724f8f)